This video gives a brief introduction to the Arclight's device.
Once attached, the sideshole of the direct ophthalmoscope will be placed directly over the
center of the lens that your mobile camera uses in the video mode.
The camera will function just like your eyes,
when you are looking through the sideshole.
To confirm which lens to line up the sidehole
with, open the video app, or click on it.
your phone.
Place your finger over each lens in turn.
When the screen goes dark,
you have covered the lens used for video.
Remove the yellow paper from the back of
the clip.
Place the points of the arrow over the center of the lens used to capture
video.
Press the clip down firmly.
Remove the arrow.
The clip should now be in the
correct position.
To video the reflex switch on the barectophthalboscope, end
off the acleights and select the brightest light with three clicks.
Make
sure the lens rack is at the top.
With the light facing away from the phone
towards the patient, place the acleights in the clip and pull the elastic over to
secure.
Push the acleights up until it cannot slide any further.
The slides hold
of the director of the most scope will now be directly over the center
of the lens that's
capture video.
To record the external eye, use the other end of the device.
To capture image now,
open the video up and zoom in filling the screen with the view through the site's home.
Press
record and perform the examination.
Press stop and save the video.
You can now share with colleagues
on secure encrypted platforms only
for the purpose you gained
concept from the patients.
Enjoy using the app lights in life.